<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>The Dragunova Collection</name>
	<author>ValiDragunova / SuviIlyaDragunova / XxHyde840xX</author>
	<supportedVersions>
			<li>1.4</li>
  	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>840.Dragunova.Combined</packageId>
	<description>THIS MOD CONTAINS THE FOLLOWING:
	
== Charged - Arsenal ==
	
\\INFO\\
From the regal tech-lodges of Gjallarhorn comes an offering of high-end spacer-level melee weapons to suit the melee-centric connoisseur. Utilizing the same pulse-charge technology seeing much use in your favorite charge projectile weapons in a proprietary magnetic confinement shelling process, your favorite melee implements become powerful, high-frequency cutting, stabbing, and bludgeoning weapons that will satisfy you with its combat performance, high-end looks, and ease of use with Gjallarhorn's well-known energy matrix lattice pattern for life-long uptime.

== Charged Arsenal - Eltex Series ==
	
\\INFO\\
From the regal tech-lodges of Gjallarhorn comes an offering of advanced high-end eltex-weaved melee weapons to suit the psionically gifted melee connoisseur. Utilizing the successful magnetic confinement shelling technique to create pulse-charged blades as a baseline, these eltex-weaved melee implements offer excellent combat performance, excellent armor penetration capability, and "sublime psionic flow", the Eltex Series is the choice for any gifted among us.

== Ilya Tech - Core ==
	
\\INFO\\
Adds Variety of Heavy High Tech Technology developed by Ilya Tech from Gjallarhorn Empire.

== Vali's Ancient Crystals - Zaljerem's Continuation ==

\\INFO\\
An alternative for Medieval Fantasy Heaters and Coolers. Ancient Midgard Crystals are a type of crystal that are said to have originated on a Volcanic/Geo-Active Planet.

STEAM IDs: 2807241532 / 2808676990 / 2800776443 / 2961062673

ORIGINAL MODs: 

https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2807241532
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2808676990
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2800776443
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2961062673

-----------
CHANGELOG:
-----------

2023/09/14

- Removed 1.3 version tags and CE stuff. No previous versions or CE here. Period.
- Combined Charged Arsenal and Eltex Series.
- Combined Ilya Tech and Vali's Ancient Crystals.
- Downscaled textures across the board.
- Tweaked hue and saturation values for Charged Eltex and Eltex Series.
- Removed "shell" tag for Defisa armor.

- Changed preview image.

===============
| XxHyde840xX |
===============
	</description>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>Victor.PsyUltra</li>
	</loadBefore>
</ModMetaData>